One of our last finishing touches for our underwater mural are bubbles and for bubbles we're going to use more of our foam brushes.
Now unlike some of our last square foam brushes, these are circular and these are excellent for, first off, you can stamp it, eyes.
You can also be used to make bubbles and other circular shapes.
So, you're going to take both of these, we're going to have our lighter paint color and we're going to lightly dip these in here.
Now the trick is to not make the bubbles appear super solid.
Bubbles are translucent.
They are not always exactly the same.
Basically what you're going to do is take your foam brush, put paint on the top and put it on here.
You can rotate there ground a little bit.
So there you go, you just get sort of a bubble.
You can have more of these going up.
I find it's really useful, when you're basically putting down your bubble, go down and then rotate about 180 degrees.
About a half circle and then to pull away.
You can see these are already looking a lot more like bubbles.
Now we don't want just bubbles of the same shape which is why I recommend also using the smaller circular foam brush.
Again the exact same strategy as with the other one.
We're going to put some paint on here, not to thick and then we're going to put it on here, do a little half circle, pull away.
Same thing over here and so on.
Now you can see you're starting to get like a nice little bubbling effect here coming up from our sand castle and around our crab area.
That's what we want to continue to do.
Once you learn how to do this, it starts to get very easy, very quick to do.
The one thing I will advise you against though, is don't make to many bubbles in the same area because after a while it will start to look crowded and cluttered and this is underwater.
You have some occasional bubbles going upwards but that's about it.
Now that we've finished putting bubbles on our mural, let's take a second to look at the different areas of the mural and the final product that we've worked towards today.
You can see how the colors have all come together and helped make you make a very special mural yourself.